[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Why did you agree to come back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well, I thought maybe we could help you sell some more newspapers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "More newspapers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Increase your viewership.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "You're aware of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "I'm sorry, yes, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "If you're at the meeting with the Vice President Biden tomorrow, with the NRA and Wal-Mart and others, what would you be saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "RATT: That the discussion has not been going anywhere that we can tell in a productive way.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA", "Wal-Mart"], "PERSON": ["Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Right, so your solution if you were there in that meeting would be to arm every school, every church, every hospital, everywhere that members of the public can be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "You certainly would want to encourage people who are qualified to carry concealed firearm to be able to do so in a school zone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Virginia"]}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "So why on earth would the fact that it's a gun free zone make any difference to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "IN", "JJ", "MD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "They're looking for -- it would seem in their sick minds to see if they can out-do the Virginia Tech slaughter, or some other thing that might be in their perverted minds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Virginia Tech"]}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "So why should we give them a neon sign that says well, see if you can do better than the last guy over here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "But you know there were armed people at Virginia Tech.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "My point to you, Mr. Pratt, is that even where you have a mass of well trained people and a mass of firearms you can still have massacres, you'd accept that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Especially if you're telling the potential victim you can't be armed.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Pratt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Do you know of those 62 mass shootings how many times a civilian has actually taken out the shooter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "It is probably not that many because we make it so hard for people to be able to defend themselves.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "WP", "VBN", "DT", ":", "RB", "CD", ",", "CC", "JJ", "-NONE-", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Why do you know more about the impact and capability of the assault weapon than General McChrystal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "While the general was busy defending the country much of the time outside of the country, understandably he may not have noticed the Korean merchants who used an -- not one, but many AR-15 rifles with large magazines to defend themselves --", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["General McChrystal"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "When was that, Mr. Pratt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "-- against the mobs -- during the Los Angeles riots.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Pratt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", ",", "WP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "When was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "That was some, what, 20 years ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "PRP", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Did you know how long ago that was, Mr. Pratt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "We're able -- let me finish my point if you would.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Pratt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Why do you feel so strongly that civilians, despite what we just heard from a leading general, should still be able to have access to these killing machines?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Well, because the general and his troops are not going to be there to protect the average American, the military nor the police after social order implodes, after a hurricane, after an earthquake, during riots.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "VB", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Why do you still persist in trying to persuade Americans that the complete opposite is true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Well, first of all, according to you investigature (ph) of the constabulary, the data that you're using for the murder rate in England is a sham.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "That's what you're saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "That's exactly what your own Constabulary is saying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Mr. Pratt, you are stating -- you are telling me on CNN we had how many gun murders last year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Nine hundred seventy and you have a violent crime rate that is the fourth highest in any country in the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Pratt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "What did you make of Mr. Jones' performance on the interview?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Well, it seemed that you had improved your demeanor quite a bit from my own experience with you and I congratulate you for maintaining it during that whole interview.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Jones"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Do you believe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "That's what our founders believed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "How many guns do you want in America, Mr. Pratt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "That's not for me to decide.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Pratt"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Do you think every American should have an AR-15?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Every American should be able to get an AR-15.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "What are you going to do if President Obama wins his battle and brings in new stricter gun control legislation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Well, he's not going to do it by legislative, in my opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "George III"]}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "You're likening President Obama to George III?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Well, he -- President Obama hasn't banned the importation of ball and powder yet, which George III did, but that was one of the major contributory elements to our war-free independence.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "George III"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Where' the humanity in doing nothing after these massacres?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "The humanity was being able to do nothing during the massacre.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "And you'd be happy with that if every school suddenly have people running around with guns, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "You're a good guesser, yes, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "CD", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "VBG", "NN", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "WDT", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Where are they going to put them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Well, when people carry a concealed firearm one doesn't exactly know for sure and the element of surprise remains with the person carry and conceal, which means that somebody contemplating doing something horrible doesn't know which person or persons might be able to arrest him, to stop him, and that's why our jurisdictions that have easy access to conceal carry firearms enjoy lower murder rates than, say, the gun control Mecca of Chicago which does better than one murder a day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 327, "question": "So I'm going to give you one more chance before we finish to say again how many gun murders you believed were in England and Wales in 2011?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "More important than the number of murders and it doesn't how a murder is committed, so I'm not going to really care about --", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2011"], "LOCATION": ["England", "Wales"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Can you repeat the number of gun murders that you said earlier?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "The data we have seen was 970.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "RBR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "What did you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "I definitely think, Piers, that more guns are not the answer, because that puts that many more guns in the hands of people who have mental illness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "When you hear somebody like Larry Pratt being so adamant, the only way to ever deal with this is to plunge ever more guns into circulation, what is your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "I struggle with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry Pratt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "When you hear this argument all the time that it all comes down to a right to bear arms under the Second Amendment of the United States Constitution, what do you think of that argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Well, seeing as it is -- this will be my 4th time with gun violence, in just the short, you know, couple year period, it is -- I don't know how to put it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States Constitution"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Have you heard any good argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Where do you think this all washes up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Well, that's a great question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "CD", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 460, "question": "What's a dangerous and unusual weapon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I would argue an AR 15 that can unload 100 bullets in a minute is a dangerous weapon under that --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House"], "LOCATION": ["Paris"], "PERSON": ["Jefferson"]}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Is that true or anything like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Well, Jefferson was actually coming back from Paris when the Bill of Rights was introduced and adopted by the House.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Arianna, where were you when you heard or saw the Alex Jones interview?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Well actually, I was here.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex Jones"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "How stressful is all of this for you, Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Well, not that stressful, because the president today has made it clear in an official statement that I am staying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "What do you make of this persistent claim from the NRA and the gun rights lobbyists that more guns means a safer America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NNS", "WDT", "JJR", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Well it is, of course, an insane claim.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}]